It's always important
to remember to maintain.
I contact
when you're talking to your boss.
Here's a binder of all the value
props around going
to the Global link next conference.
So pretend I'm your boss.
Walk me through the list,
but be sure to maintain
eye contact with me.
Okay,
Global ink. Next.
Also
eyes up here, buddy.
Global Link. Next conference
is a fellow is a eyes on name.
It's a conference about globalization.
And
look, I don't think I can read it
without reading.
Change fifty two
to "know what you're going to say".
And if you still need help convincing
your boss to send you to global ink.
Next, cut that link Tiger.
His pants were brand new,
but Scotch is eighteen years old.